commsec.com.au 2014-12-19

# Learn about our Privacy Policy - CommBank

In our increasingly digital world, we take our responsibility to protect your privacy very seriously by applying strict security and privacy controls to the way we handle your personal information. We use the information you provide us to give you the best possible banking experiences, to help us assess your applications as well as design and tailor products and services so they’re just right for you.

View our short videos for more information:

Your privacy in the digital world

When we use your information

Innovating with privacy in mind

It’s about trust  

We know that how we collect, use, exchange and protect your information is important to you, and we value your trust. Our Privacy Policy outlines how we do this, in accordance with the Privacy Act and the Australian Privacy Principles. It covers:

  * About the Commonwealth Bank Group
  * Information we collect
  * How we use your information
  * Who we exchange your information with
  * Credit checks and credit reporting
  * Keeping your information secure
  * Accessing, updating and correcting your information
  * Making a privacy complaint
  * How to contact us and find out more. 

Our Privacy Policy is for customers of the Group. It also includes our policy on the handling of credit reports and other credit-related information. Some of our Australian business units and subsidiaries have separate policies that are consistent with our Group policy. See section 10 of the Privacy Policy.

If you're a customer of one of our overseas subsidiaries, then the privacy policy of that organisation may reflect local conditions and legal requirements. If you're a customer of these business units or subsidiaries, please refer to their policy.

During the course of our relationship with you, we may tell you more about how we handle your information, such as when you complete an application or claims form, or receive terms and conditions or a Product Disclosure Statement. When you receive this information, please consider it carefully.

We update our policy from time-to-time, so refer to this page for the latest version. If you have any questions, please contact us.  

Important credit reporting information
